♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 14=
Stop!
Governor Xu, what brings you here?
Since when did this place belong to you?
You should be grateful and kowtow to me
that I don't charge you with a crime
for breaking into this place.
Governor Xu, don't be so arrogant.
Aren't you afraid
that you'll die a miserable death
once you fall?
Rest assured, President Du.
You won't live to see that day.
Let's go.
Darn it! How dare he talk nonsense here!
(It seems Rong Xiaonan
took the phoenix crown before them.)
(The Xiaosheng Society cares so much
about the Buddha Head and phoenix crown.)
(What exactly are they after?)
Send men to station here.
Don't let anyone in.
Besides, hide that fake Buddha Head
and don't let anyone know.
Yes!
(Right now, the only way
to keep the Xiaosheng Society in check)
(is to hold the Buddha Head
in my hands.)
Miss, a guest is here.
Miss Jiang,
I'm Song Mianxiang, the coroner.
I need to see Governor.
Oh.
Dr. Song,
he is not in the residence right now.
If you have urgent business,
I can let the maid take you
to the main hall to wait.
Dr. Song, what do you want?
I came to deliver
a document to Governor,
concerning the real murderer
of the case from eight years ago.
I told you
if you have urgent business,
go wait in the main hall.
Besides seeing Governor,
I also wanted to see what kind of woman
can make Governor fall for her.
So you are using official business
as an excuse
to discuss personal matters
with Governor?
Miss Jiang, would you be interested
in hearing about this personal matter?
You wait outside.
Yes.
Don't scream,
or I'll silence you forever.
Wait.
We don't even know each other,
nor do we have any grudge.
What are you doing now?
We don't know each other?
We have no grudge?
Eight years ago,
I was abducted to the Jiang family,
and forced to learn opera
from your mother
to serve men.
Your father abused me,
humiliated me,
even forced me to serve those big shots,
in exchange for benefits.
The Jiang family is the culprit
that brought me suffering.
Impossible!
Nonsense!
My parents were honorable
throughout their lives.
To think you can tarnish
their reputation with some nonsense?
Are you pretending
or have you really forgotten?
Fine.
No matter what,
I'll help you remember.
(Gu Fengqiu, Jiang Chun'er's mother)
Learn it hard.
(Young Jiang Chun'er)
Look up.
Take Chun'er away.
Yes.
(Governor Mansion)
Xu You'an.
Drive him away.
Mr. Rong, please leave.
The one who killed your mother
wasn't my master.
He was framed.
The murderers were Xu Fan
and Jiang Xiaoren.
They lured and abused women.
To cover up their crimes,
they murdered them
and framed my master.
Chun'er.
Stop!
Song Mianxiang?
Why is she in the Governor Mansion?
What happened to Chun'er?
I don't know.
Just now, Miss Jiang was talking
with a doctor named Song Mianxiang.
Soon, screams came from the room.
Song Mianxiang?
You may leave now.
Yes.
Governor,
we found Song Mianxiang's home.
Are you okay?
Xu You'an.
M-My father wouldn't do that.
He was a good man.
He was so good to me.
How could he be such a person?
Who told you this?
What exactly happened?
What did Song Mianxiang tell you?
She pricked me with a needle.
Then I saw my father forcing
a group of girls to learn opera
and serve others.
H-He even killed people.
(Could what Rong Xiaonan said be true?)
This can't be true, right?
But why...
But why have I never
remembered this before?
I don't remember anything.
Anything...
It's okay.
The doctor said
you need to rest for a while.
I will get to the bottom of this.
Don't worry. I'm here.
Interesting!
They're investigating the case
from eight years ago.
Before they find out the truth,
have your people incite the public
to push Jiang Chun'er to her death,
and seize the chance to pull Xu You'an
down from the Governor position.
I haven't found the phoenix crown.
Why would I trust you once more?
If the truth from eight years ago
comes to light,
not to mention obtaining
the phoenix crown and Jade Buddha Head,
your Xiaosheng Society and the Japanese
might not even be able
to keep a foothold in Fengcheng.
Can those ignorant people
hold them back?
Xu You'an won't kill civilians,
but he's impulsive by nature.
If he's provoked, and accidentally
kills some ignorant people,
then we can incite all the people
of the city to overthrow him.
Governor Xu.
What a rare guest.
Who are you?
Just someone
who almost died eight years ago.
Eight years ago?
Xu You'an,
I overestimated you.
I know
that your mother was also killed
by Jiang Xiaoren and his men.
I thought you could solve the case
from eight years ago.
As expected, men cannot be trusted.
My mother
was killed by President Jiang?
Zhao Shengge was not the murderer?
Ridiculous!
Even I could figure out the truth,
yet you cannot?
Come to Governor Mansion with me.
I will figure out the truth.
What did you do?
Just lit some datura.
You won't die for now.
I'll give you one last chance.
Don't make any more mistakes.
It's not worth risking your life.
Chance?
Let me tell you,
in this world, there is no place
to even raise a grievance.
Other than petitioning with my life,
what else can I do?
I thought you would be different,
but it seems you're all the same.
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪